Guide to the Judith Hancock de Sandoval papers and photographs
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- June 2002 Acquisition, 1907-1997; 16.2; (31 boxes) and 68 broadsides
  - Oversize, 0.66; (4 boxes)
    - Disney's Buffalo Bill Posters, undated (Box 98 (Oversize))
- June 2012 Acquisition, 1986-1990; 0.21; (1 box)
  Black and white photographic prints and 35 mm transparencies by Judith Hancock de Sandoval relating to her Historic Ranches of Wyoming photographic project.
  Gift of Judith Hancock de Sandoval, 2012.
  - 35 mm transparencies, Historic Ranches of Wyoming, 1986-1990 (Box 99)
  - Black and white prints, Historic Ranches of Wyoming, 1986 (Box 99)